这是不对的
That's not right.
你这人根本不讲理呀
That's so unreasonable.
如果你要这样做
Yeah, well, if you're going to be like this,
那我也不想跟你说话了
then I don't want to talk to you right now, either.
好吧  爱你  拜拜
Okay. I love you. Bye.
在和亚马逊客服讲话吗
Amazon customer support?
不  是我妈
No, my mother.
你猜她非要我们邀请谁来参加婚礼
Guess who she's insisting we invite to our wedding.
耶稣吗
Jesus?
是就好了
If only.
是我哥哥
My brother.
等等  你没邀请你哥来参加婚礼吗
Wait a minute. You didn't invite your brother to your own wedding?
我的整个童年都是在他的淫威下度过的
He tormented me my whole childhood.
这样的行为怎么能配获得
I don't think I should reward that type of behavior
《星球大战》系列中的宇宙飞船
吃上一块千年隼形状结婚蛋糕的机会呢
with a slice of wedding cake in the shape of the Millennium Falcon.
你再说一遍
Try again.
一块蛋糕形状的结婚蛋糕
A slice of wedding cake in the shape of a cake.
也许他小时候对你坏了点
Look, he may have been mean to you when you were kids,
但你俩现在都是成年人了
but you're both grown men now.
没错  我成年了
That's right. I'm a grown-up,
如果我不想让他参加我婚礼  我就不用邀请他
and if I don't want to invite him to my wedding, then I won't.
好吧
Okay.
可我不得不邀请  因为我妈咪逼我做
Except I have to 'cause my mommy's making me.
第十一季  第二十三集
每个迎宾礼袋中含有一张婚礼时间表
Okay, so each welcome bag gets a schedule of events,
一份地图和我送的巧克力
a map, and chocolate from me.
谢尔顿送的一瓶免冲洗手液
And from Sheldon, a bottle of Purell...
以及如果有人误喝了洗手液
...the number for Poison Control in case someone
需要拨打的毒物控制中心电话
accidentally drinks the Purell,
以及一张压膜的元素周期表
and a laminated table of elements
因为美国的学校系统就是垃圾
because the American school system is a failure.
有多少客人是从外地来的
How many out-of-town guests are there gonna be?
我还真不知道
I'm actually not sure.
我才发现谢尔顿没有邀请他哥哥
Turns out Sheldon didn't invite his brother.
现在开始有婚礼的感觉了
Mm. Now it's starting to sound like a wedding.
如果他哥不来  他妈也不肯来了
And his mom said she won't come if his brother's not there.
现在开始有完美婚礼的感觉了
Ooh, now it's starting to sound like a good wedding.
妮妮
Hey, Bernie.
红眼病的症状是什么来着
How do you know if someone has pink eye?
眼睛发红  变肿  还有分泌物
Um, their eye would be red, swollen and probably oozy.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
咱家俩娃都得了红眼病
Both kids have pink eye.
不会吧
Oh, no.
你站着别动
You stop right there.
我下周就要结婚了
I'm getting married in a week;
你可不能把红眼病传染给我
you are not giving me pink eye.
我又没得红眼病
I don't have pink eye.
慢着  慢着  慢着
Hey! Hey. Hey.
别靠近新娘
Step away from the bride.
好  那我回楼上去了
Okay. I'll go back upstairs.
赶紧去冲澡  然后把这身衣服都烧了
Get in the shower and then take those clothes and burn them.
没错  把你其他衣服一起烧了
Yeah, and all the rest of your clothes!
值得一试嘛
Ah, worth a shot.
我是不是谢尔顿婚礼上唯一单身的人
So am I gonna be, like, the only single guy at Sheldon's wedding?
不
No.
还有好多单身人士在呢
There-There'll be a lot of single people there.
斯图尔特  艾米的姑姥姥
Stuart, Amy's great-aunt...
不过  斯图尔特加她脸书好友了
Although, Stuart's already friended her on Facebook,
所以你最好抓紧动作
so, better move quick.
我必须找个伴了
I got to find a date.
我才不想做
I don't want to be that sad single friend
被众人报以同情目光的可怜单身狗
that everyone looks at with pity.
我想这已经是无法挽回的事实了
Uh, I'm-I'm afraid that ship may have sailed.
莱纳德
Leonard,
你也有哥哥对吧
you have a brother, right?
对
Yes.
他是不是特讨厌
Is he the worst?
是不是可恶到令人发指
Is he an unspeakable abomination?
是不是一想到他就让你毛骨悚然
Does the very thought of him make your skin crawl?
他除了会说完笑话自己笑之外
Well, he laughs at his own jokes,
其他方面还算不错啦
but otherwise he's okay.
谢尔顿  你怎么了
Sheldon, what's going on?
我要邀请我那个傻大哥来参加婚礼
I'm trying to invite my stupid brother to my wedding
可他故意不接我电话
and he's avoiding my calls.
你怎么知道他故意不接你电话
You don't know he's avoiding your calls.
你好  我是乔治·库珀
Hey, you've reached George Cooper.
有事请留言  但如果你是谢尔顿
Please leave a message, unless this is Sheldon again,
那么请拨打我的另一个号码
in which case, please try me on my other number,
1-800-去死-吧
1-800-suck-it.
听到没
See?
我知道那号码是假的
And I know that's not a real number
谁会给自己弄个免费专线呀
because why would it be toll-free?
谢尔顿  你尝试过了
Sheldon, you tried.
你也没有其他办法了
What more could you have done?
你为什么一开始不邀请他呢
Hey, why didn't you invite him in the first place?
你不懂和他一起长大的恐怖体验
You don't know what it was like growing up with him.
我懂  我兄弟多着呢
I get it; I grew up with lots of brothers.
我哥阿杜特就特别坏
My brother Adoot was especially mean.
真的吗  我从没听你说过阿杜特
Really? I've never heard you mention Adoot.
我当然说过
Yeah, sure I have.
小时候就是他忘了关门
He's the one who left the door open when we were kids,
害我的宠物猫鼬跑掉了
and my pet mongoose ran away.
白痴阿杜特
Stupid Adoot.
除了搭飞机亲自去找他
Look, uh, short of getting on a plane and flying there,
你妈还指望你怎么做呢
what does your mother expect you to do?
我一直在说我不要
I kept saying no.
我怎么就坐上来了呢
H-H-How am I here?
我告诉你没
Hey, did I tell you?
-我找到个伴了  -去参加婚礼吗
- I found a date. - ?To the wedding?
不  去喝咖啡
Uh, to coffee.
但如果进行顺利  谢尔顿和艾米的婚礼上见
But if things go well, Sheldon and Amy's wedding.
你不会担心邀请一个
Aren't you worried it's a little intense
刚认识的人参加婚礼会把人逼得太紧吗
to ask someone you just met to go to a wedding?
我时间要不够了
I'm running out of time.
怎么没人开发一种服务
Wh-Wh-Why can't there be a service where you can
可以付钱请人假装当一晚你的伴侣呢
just pay someone to be your date for the evening?
就像三陪服务吗
Like an escort service?
不  不  不  不是付钱和她上床
No, no, no. Y-You wouldn't be paying for sex.
虽然如果进展顺利
I mean, obviously if things went well,
那自然会上床  但你主要是付钱请她
it could lead to sex, but, but the money is for,
花时间陪伴你
like, you know, her time and companionship.
我明白了
Oh, I get it...
三陪服务
an escort service.
别再这么说了
Stop saying that.
别再不谋而合了
Stop meaning it.
拉杰还记得你那天
Hey, Raj, remember when you borrowed
借走我的虚拟实境眼镜吗
my VR goggles the other day?
记得
Yeah.
真不是个好主意啊
Probably shouldn't have done that.
轮胎医生
等等  你哥就是轮胎医生吗
So, wait, y-your brother is Dr. Tire?
是的  而且呢
Yes, and, apparently,
只需要读半学期的社区大学
it only takes half a semester of community college
就能得到这个医生文凭
to get that particular doctorate.
我们一路上经过了三家分店呢
We passed three of these stores on the way here.
你为什么会说他是"卖轮胎的废柴"
Why did you say he's just "some loser who sells tires"?
你说得对  我那话有失公允
You're right, that was unfair.
他是全德州轮胎销售量最高的废柴
He's a loser who sells more tires than anyone in Texas.
打扰了
Oh, excuse me.
我们想找小乔治·库珀
Uh, we're looking for a Georgie Cooper.
稍等片刻  我去看一下医生在不在
One second, I'll check to see if the doctor's in.
他才不是医生
He is not a doctor.
在场只有一个博士[医生]  那就是我
There's only one doctor here and it's me.
我也是博士啊
I'm also a doctor.
你想回车上等吗
Do you want to wait in the car?
我想在加州等啊
I wanted to wait in California.
他就是小乔治吗
So, is this Georgie?
是啊
Yes.
他用那个听诊器
And what is he even using
是想要听出个什么鬼啊
that stethoscope to listen to?
不知道啊  微小的漏气吗
I don't know, small leak?
好吧  这合理
All right, that makes sense.
你他妈来这里干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
你好  小乔治
Hello, Georgie.
现在叫乔治就行了
It's just George now.
好吧  乔治
Fine, George.
不行  人家不喜欢  小乔治
No, I don't like it-- Georgie.
我看你真是一点都没变啊
I see you haven't changed one bit.
谢谢你  这话真动听
Thank you, that is a nice thing to say.
你好  我是莱纳德
Hey, I'm Leonard.
我来是因为....  毫无理由
I'm here for-for no reason.
你想怎么样  谢尔顿
What do you want, Sheldon?
你为什么不回我的电话
Why aren't you returning my phone calls?
你才应该是聪明的那个
You're supposed to be the smart one;
你自己想
you figure it out.
他不是这种聪明
He's not that kind of smart.
你最好给他一点提示
You might want to give him a hint.
我们有十多年没说过话了
We haven't talked in over ten years,
现在你有事求我
and now that you need something,
你以为你就可以直接跑来我店里吗
you think you can just show up at my store?
我们把手头事情都先放一边
Well, let's just drop everything
先满足谢尔顿吧
to accommodate Sheldon.
你少来
Nice try,
我不再是容易上当的小男孩了
but I am not a gullible little boy anymore.
我现在能听出话中带刺
I can recognize sarcasm.
好吧  你说得对
Okay. You're right.
抱歉
I'm-I'm-I'm sorry.
告诉我你有何需要
Tell me what you need.
您的愿望对我就是圣旨
Your wish is my command.
这次好多了  谢谢
That's better, thank you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
对  我也得了
Yeah, I got it, too.
你真是不碰霍华德会死  是吧
Wow. You really can't keep your hands off Howard, can you?
我知道  我有病
I know, I have a problem.
我就想确认你跟艾米没得红眼病
I just wanted to make sure you and Amy didn't get it.
我是没得啦
Well, I didn't get it.
你在我婚礼前一周传染给我了
You infected me a week before my wedding.
我该怎么解决这个
What am I supposed to do about this?
戴上面纱
Wear a veil?
一点都不好笑
It's not funny.
看看你对我做了什么
Look at what you've done to me!
你能不能  别碰我的电脑
Could you just, like, not touch my computer
或是其他东西  我...
or... like, anything else. I just, ugh,
我不想在你婚礼照片上留下这副丑样儿
I don't want to look like that in your wedding photos.
不会有什么婚礼照片了
There aren't gonna be any wedding photos.
我的未婚夫有洁癖
My fiancé's a germophobe.
要是被他发现我得了传染病
If he finds out I'm contagious,
他就会永远留在德州不回来了
he'll never come back from Texas.
如果我们告诉他  婚礼主题是《行尸走肉》
What if we tell him the theme of the wedding is Walking Dead
这是我们的丧尸妆怎么样
and this is our zombie makeup?
这应该能行
That'll probably work.
我们先把这列为B计划
We'll call that plan B.
好吧
Oh, well...
结果这个东西还是有用武之处的啊
Turns out this is gonna come in handy after all.
等一下  我没听明白
Hold up. I-I'm confused.
你不想我参加你的婚礼
You didn't want me at your wedding,
但现在妈不愿意来
but now that Mom won't come,
你就希望我参加了
you want me there.
我知道你不常听到这话
I know you don't hear this a lot,
但你说得完全正确
but that is exactly right.
干得好
Good job.
这是火上浇油  谢尔顿
Not helping, Sheldon.
听好了
Listen here,
你希望我参加你的婚礼
you want me at your wedding,
你只需礼貌地问我就行了
all you got to do is ask nicely.
-小乔治  -是乔治
- Georgie. - ?George.
我希望你能来参加我的婚礼
I would like you at my wedding.
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
听见这话真暖心
That is so nice to hear.
但我宁可吞掉一只怀孕的野猫
But I would rather swallow a pregnant wildcat
并拉出一窝小奶猫也不去
and crap out a litter of kittens.
你做轮胎行业最适合不过了
It is fitting that you got into tires,
因为你"胎"讨厌了
because you are tiresome.
谢尔顿  过来
Sheldon, come on.
我说得太恶毒了吗
Was that too mean?
不算太恶毒  但哏也有点烂
No, not too mean, not too good either.
不  妈妈  这不公平
No, Mother. That's not fair.
但他对我说...
But he told...
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
但我说...
But I said...
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
再见
Good-bye.
她怎么说
What'd she say?
她不会插手
She's not getting in the middle of it
因为我们"兄弟俩得自己解决问题"
because we "boys need to work it out ourselves."
她不来参加婚礼或许也没关系
Oh, maybe it's fine if she doesn't come to the wedding.
我现在有艾米了
I've got Amy now,
妈妈能做的她都能做  还远不止此
and she can do everything a mom can do and more.
洞房花烛夜对她说这句话
Say that to her on the wedding night.
能增添情趣呢
Really spice things up.
这都是小乔治的错
This is all Georgie's fault.
我整个童年时期他都欺负我
My whole childhood, he was mean to me.
辛苦了  我知道跟一个恶霸同住是什么感觉
Sorry. I know what it's like to live with a bully.
你哥哥也欺负你吗
Your brother bullied you?
我说的是佩妮  不过他当然也有
Oh, I was talking about Penny, but sure, yeah.
我八岁那一次
Once, when I was eight,
我准备在万圣节扮成我最喜欢的科学家
I was going to dress as my favorite scientist for Halloween,
小乔治竟然把我的服装扔了
and Georgie threw my costume away.
我不得不罩上床单  扮成鬼
I had to wear a sheet and go as a ghost.
整晚都吓死我自己了
Scared myself all night long.
我们明早才飞走
Well, look, we don't fly out until the morning.
不如我去跟他谈谈  再试一次
Why don't I try and talk to him, give it one more shot?
好吧
All right.
但如果他说  "书呆说什么"
But if he says, "Nerd says what,"
-别回答他  -什么
- Don't answer him. - ?What?
你犹如待宰的羔羊
You are a lamb to the slaughter.
你的约会怎么样
So, how was your date?
本来很顺利  直到我眼睛分泌物滴进她咖啡
It was going well until my eye dripped in her latte.
很抱歉我们毁了你的约会
We're so sorry we ruined your date.
真是可怜呢
Oh, boo-hoo.
他的约会毁了
His date got ruined.
我可是快结婚了  看看我
I'm about to get married, and look at me.
看起来有好转了
It looks like it's getting better.
是吗
Oh, does it?
你两只清澈明亮的眼睛看到的吗
Does it look like that with your two clear eyes?
不好意思  你是在气我没得红眼病吗
I'm sorry. Are you mad that I don't have pink eye?
-你说呢  -没错
- What do you think? - Yes!
好的
Uh-huh. Okay.
好的  我听到了
Okay. Uh, uh, listen, I hear you.
美国职橄球联盟史上最成功的的球队之一
我知道很贵  但这些可是轮胎中的达拉斯牛仔队
I know they're pricey, but these are the Dallas Cowboys of tires, okay?
均为牛仔队的四分卫
我说的可是特洛伊·艾克曼时期的牛仔队
And we're talking the Troy Aikman Cowboys,
可不是小白脸托尼·罗莫时期
not that pretty boy Tony Romo.
好的  好选择
All right. Good call.
你不会后悔的
You won't regret it.
炸裂
Boom! ?
好厉害啊
Wow. That was impressive. Yeah.
这并不难  只要你热爱自己的产品
Well, it's easy when you love your product
以及讨厌托尼·罗莫
and hate Tony Romo.
是啊  那家伙真是...
Yeah, that guy's the...
其实我不知道他是谁
Actually, I don't, I don't know who that guy is.
如果你是来当谢尔顿婚礼的说客  省省吧
If you are here about Sheldon's wedding, don't bother.
别这样  我知道你俩有些[意见]不同
Come on. I-I know you two have your differences.
你是指基本上在所有方面都不同吗
You mean pretty much everything about us?
也不是所有方面啦
Well, not everything.
你们都很高  你们的姓氏都一样
You're both tall, you have the same last name.
也许我一开始不应该说得好像能列出很多条
Maybe I shouldn't have started this like it was a list.
你根本不知道自己在说什么
You have no idea what you are talking about.
你看  这语气像极了谢尔顿
Ooh, there-- that-that was very Sheldon.
我很肯定他不是好相处的弟弟
Look, I-I'm sure he was not the easiest brother to have,
但他也不好过
but it wasn't easy for him either,
因为你经常欺负他
with you picking on him all the time.
欺负他  他是这么说的吗
Picking on him? Is that what he told you?
比如那一次
Well, what about the time
你扔掉他的万圣节服饰呢
you threw away his Halloween costume?
但那是因为他想打扮成女科学家啊
Well, yeah, 'cause he was gonna dress as some girl scientist.
居里夫人吗
Madame Curie?
我不知道她还是个鸨母[夫人]啊
Oh, I didn't know she was a madam.
拜托  他穿那个裙子  我不揍也会有别人揍
Come on. He was still gonna get beat up for wearing that dress.
你不是还在他要看
Well, didn't you sit on his head
《星际迷航》的时候坐他头上了吗
while he tried to watch Star Trek?
对啊  可是那样超好笑
Well, yeah, but that was hilarious.
的确是还挺好笑的
That is pretty hilarious, yeah.
拜托  以前上学时我总罩着他
Look, I mean, I always looked out for him at school.
我开车载他到处去
I drove him everywhere.
他失礼时我替他跟人赔不是
I apologized to people when he was rude.
这些我也全做了
Yeah. I've done all that.
我还帮他挑掉爱尔兰小精灵麦片里
I've also removed all the red balloons from his Lucky Charms
他觉得不够"爱尔兰"的红色气球状麦片
because they weren't "Irish enough."
那你应该懂我说的意思啊
All right. So you know what I'm talking about.
那他可曾谢过你
And has he ever thanked you?
没用太多言语...
Not in so many words,
或任何言语说过
or any words.
那让他表达感激一下是会死吗
Would it kill him to actually say it?
不  的确不会死
No. No, it wouldn't kill him.
莱纳德
Leonard,
你知道我是怎么拿到钱
you know how I got the money
来开我第一家店的吗
to open up my first store?
是我拼了老命弄来的
I busted my ass for it,
因为我家多余的钱全都要给谢尔顿
'cause all the extra money that we had had to go to Sheldon
好供他上大学和去德国读书
so he could go to college and he could go study in Germany.
你知道他从没对我说过什么吗
And do you know what he's never said to me?
当颗藓
Danke schon?
这是"谢谢"的德语
It's, uh, "thank you" in German.
需要我也坐到你脑袋上吗
Do you need me to sit on your head?
不用了
Nope.
在我牺牲了那么多之后
After all my sacrifices,
你猜我妈最以哪个孩子为荣
guess which kid my mom is the most proud of.
不知道这话能不能安慰到你
If it makes you feel any better,
但我妈最引以为荣的也是谢尔顿  所以...
my mom's most proud of Sheldon, too, so...
莱纳德
Leonard,
要来瓶啤酒吗
you want a beer?
我愿意来瓶啤酒
Yeah, I would love a beer.
给
There you go.
-谢谢  你能帮忙我打开吗  -这是拧开的那种
- Thanks. Can you open it for me? - No, it's a twist-off.
我知道
I know.
看
Hey!
我把所有珠珠都弄到另一边了
I got all the beads to the other side.
佩妮  这又不是什么谜题
It's not a puzzle, Penny.
你确定你要碰那些东西吗
Do you really want to be touching that?
你知道有多少生病的孩子摸...
Do you know how many sick kids...?
算了没事  你尽量玩
You know, never mind. Knock yourself out.
伯纳黛特说他们在检查孩子了
Bernadette says they're checking the kids now.
其实我们不用全部都来的吧
You know, maybe we didn't all need to come.
他们孩子得了哪种红眼病  我就得了哪种
Hey, whatever kind of pink eye their kids have, I have,
我需要知道情况
and I need to know.
如果是病毒性的  那我惨了
And if it's viral, I'm screwed.
不一定  我知道这不算传统婚礼服饰
Maybe not. You know, I know it's not traditional wedding attire,
但焊工面罩你觉得如何
but how about a welder's mask?
如果你认识焊工
If you know a welder,
美国婚礼习俗  婚礼需要准备四样东西
分别是新的  旧的  借的  蓝的
那面罩可以算你"借来的东西"
that could be your "something borrowed."
好消息  是好治的细菌性
Great news! It's bacterial!
-太好了  -棒
- Yeah! ?- Yeah. ?Yes!
-赞啦  -耶
- Yeah. ?- Yes. ?
你们在干嘛  快去洗手
What are you doing?! Wash your hands!
你不必了
Oh. ?Not you.
你好  客房服务吗
Hello. Room service?
我打来是想说一下你们的总汇三明治
I'm calling about the club sandwich on your menu.
不  我没有要点
No, I-I don't want one.
我只是想纠正你们的错字
I just want you to spell it correctly.
除非你们的"总会"是指总会写错字
Unless the "Club" is the Poor Typing Club.
好
Okay.
现在来说你们的15%小"废"
Now let's discuss this 15% "gratooty"?
对...  你这样也太没礼貌了
Yeah-- well, that was rude.
某人要得不到小"废"了
Someone just lost their gratooty.
谢尔顿  你得跟你哥哥道歉
Sheldon, you need to apologize to your brother.
你说什么[抱歉]
I'm sorry? ?
是的  就是这样  但面向那里语气好点
Yes. Like that, but nicer, and that way.
我没有什么好对他道歉的
I have nothing to apologize for.
我就跟你说这是烂主意
I told you this was a bad idea.
有些轮胎是补不了的
Sometimes you can't patch a tire.
你只能买新的换
You just got to buy a new one.
其实永远都是这样
Actually, that's always the case.
永远别补  汰旧换新
Never patch, buy new.
虽然我挺欣赏你的民间轮胎箴言
While I appreciate your folksy tire wisdom,
但我并不欣赏你让妈遭受的事
I don't appreciate what you're putting Mom through.
妈遭受什么你知道个鬼啊
What would you know about what Mom's been through?
你一直都不在家
You were never home.
这样挺好的
Yeah, this is good.
把不满都说出来
Get it all out. ?
-不是时候  -闭嘴
- Not now! ?- Shut up!
爸去世后你就去上了大学
You went away to college after Dad died.
你觉得是谁负责照顾了家里
Who do you think took care of everything?
妈妈啊  妈总是照顾好了一切
Mom did. Mom always took care of everything.
妈妈当时魂不守舍  米希是个中二少女
Mom was a mess, Missy was a dumb teenager.
只能我来一肩挑起照顾她们的责任
I had to look after both of 'em.
我整天都有跟妈打电话啊
I talked to Mom all the time.
她如果不开心会告诉我的吧
If she was upset, she would have told me.
她是在保护你  你个白痴
She was protecting you, you idiot,
你生活中我们所有人都这样
just like everyone always does.
如果情况那么糟糕
If things were bad,
那你为什么不告诉我
then why didn't you tell me?
因为我也在保护你啊
Because I was protecting you, too.
谢尔顿  你是我的弟弟
You're my baby brother, Sheldon.
我知道你从小就过得辛苦
I know life has been hard for you,
但这并不代表我们其他人就一帆风顺啊
but that don't mean it's been easy for the rest of us.
我好像是没有想过其他人的感受
I suppose I didn't think about how it was for everyone else.
算了  没事
No, that's all right.
我知道你没想过
I know you didn't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果我的大哥能出席我婚礼
And it would mean a lot to me
那将对我意义非常重大
to have my big brother at my wedding.
我不会错过
I wouldn't miss it.
是我错觉  还是我们刚补好了一个轮胎
Is it me, or did we just patch a tire?
他说了"永远别补"  你不听人说话的吗
He said, "never patch." do you even listen?
情况怎么样啦
Hey, how's it going?
非常好
Really good.
小乔治会来参加我们的婚礼
Georgie's going to come to the wedding.
那太好了
Oh, that's great!
你为什么不看镜头
Why aren't you looking at the camera?
我是在锻炼我的周边视觉
Oh, you know, I'm just working on my peripheral vision.
你在说什么胡话
Well, that is nonsense.
你的周边视觉好得很
Your peripheral vision is fine.
是不是那些女性杂志又让你觉得
Are those women's magazines making you feel bad
自己这里不好那里不好了
about yourself again?
是的  正是这个情况
Yup, that is what's happening.
这话我跟你说过了  杂志上的女人全都靠修图
I have told you before, those women are airbrushed
这次也是修了好看起来像有好视力
to make it look like they have good vision.
话说我想到
Hey, I-I was thinking,
现在你跟你大哥和好了
now that you and your brother made up,
你也不用着急回家啊
there's no reason to rush home.
或许你跟莱纳德可以多待...
Maybe you and Leonard could, could stay for, uh...
两到三个充满欢乐的日子后再回来啊
two to three more fun-filled days there.
真是个好主意啊
That's a great idea!
莱纳德  有好消息
Hey, Leonard, good news.
我们现在有时间去参观美国铁路博物馆了
We do have time to visit the Museum of the American Railroad!
我想拒绝  但说了又有何用
I'd say no, but what's the point?
你最好别太接近我
Ooh. You might not want to get too close.
红眼病
Pink eye.
我也是
Me, too!
-细菌性的吗  -是的
- Bacterial? - ?Yeah.
一样
Same! ?
我知道这话听起来可能很疯狂  但...
I-I know this is gonna sound crazy, but...
你会有兴趣跟我一起去参加个婚礼吗
would you be interested in going to a wedding with me?